ACTWU's Social Services Department Records 5619/023
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Human Service Workers of the American Labor Movement Incorporated, 1984 (Box 22, Folder 34)
- Humphery Hawkins Bill, 1976-1978 (Box 22, Folder 35)
- Hungary, 1991 (Box 22, Folder 36)
- Hugo Hurricane Relief Fund, 1989 (Box 22, Folder 37)
- Hurricane Andrew, 1992 (Box 22, Folder 38)
- Iceland, 1988 (Box 22, Folder 39)
- Hyper Tension Program, 1977-1985 (Box 23, Folder 1)
- Illinois State Federation of Labor, 1979-1984 (Box 23, Folder 2)
- Inter-American Dialogue, 1984-1985 (Box 23, Folder 3)
- Interest Group Politics, 1992 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  June 8
- International Affairs, 1991 (Box 23, Folder 5)
- International Foundation Employee Benefit Plans, 1974 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  February 12
- Industrial Relations Research Association, 1985-1993 (Box 23, Folder 7)
- International Chemical Workers, 1986-1990 (Box 23, Folder 8)
- International Confederation of Fair Trade Unions, 1990-1993 (Box 23, Folder 9)
- International Confederation of Fair Trade Unions, 1991-1992 (Box 23, Folder 10)
- International Confederation of Fair Trade Unions, 1990-1991 (Box 23, Folder 11)
- International Confederation of Fair Trade Unions, 1989-1990 (Box 23, Folder 12)
- International Confederation of Fair Trade Unions/Coalition of Labor Union, 1991 (Box 23, Folder 13)
- International Confederation of Fair Trade Unions - Newspaper, 1991 (Box 23, Folder 14)
  September 30
- International Confederation of Fair Trade Unions - Executive Board, 1989-1992 (Box 23, Folder 15)
- International Confederation of Fair Trade Unions - General Board, 1992 (Box 23, Folder 16)
- Venezuela, 1992 (Box 23, Folder 17)
- International Confederation of Fair Trade Unions Women's Committee World Conference, 1989-1993 (Box 23, Folder 18)
- International Confederation of Fair Trade Unions - World Women's Conference, 1989-1991 (Box 24, Folder 1)
- International Confederation of Fair Trade Unions Congress [1 of 2], 1988 (Box 24, Folder 2)
- International Confederation of Fair Trade Unions Congress [2 of 2], 1988 (Box 24, Folder 3)
- International Confederation of Fair Trade Unions Congress, 1983 (Box 24, Folder 4)
- International Confederation of Fair Trade Unions - Latin America, 1988 (Box 24, Folder 5)
- International Confederation of Fair Trade Unions - Spain, 1985-1988 (Box 24, Folder 6)
- International Confederation of Fair Trade Unions - Women's Committee, 1987 (Box 24, Folder 7)
- International Labor Office, 1988-1990 (Box 24, Folder 8)
- International Labour Organization, 1979-1991 (Box 24, Folder 9)
- International Labor Rights, 1987-1991 (Box 24, Folder 10)
- International Labor Press Association, 1977-1979 (Box 24, Folder 11)
- Industrial and Labor Relations Research Fund, 1987-1992 (Box 24, Folder 12)
- International Trade, 1983 (Box 24, Folder 13)
- Women's Year International, 1975-1978 (Box 24, Folder 14)
- International Women's Year - Houston, 1977 (Box 24, Folder 15)
  June 16
- International Women's Year - New York, 1977 (Box 24, Folder 16)
- Internal Revenue Service, 1974-1975 (Box 24, Folder 17)
- Internal Revenue Service - Assistance, 1982 (Box 24, Folder 18)
  November 3
- International Ladies Garment Workers Union, 1975-1978 (Box 24, Folder 19)
- Iowa Federation of Labor, 1985 (Box 24, Folder 20)
- Iran, 1985 (Box 24, Folder 21)
- Ireland, 1983 (Box 24, Folder 22)
- Israel, 1975-1992 (Box 24, Folder 23)
- International Union of Electrical Workers, 1974 (Box 24, Folder 24)
  July 18
- Italy, 1980 (Box 24, Folder 25)
- JFK (movie) (Box 24, Folder 26)
- J.T.R. Incorporated, 1980 (Box 24, Folder 27)
  January 7
- Job Training Partnership Act, 1988 (Box 24, Folder 28)
  October 21
- Jesse Jackson (Box 24, Folder 29)
- Immigration Law, 1987-1990 (Box 24, Folder 30)
- Import Bill, 1987-1990 (Box 24, Folder 31)
- Immigration, 1987-1992 (Box 25, Folder 1)
- Imports, 1974-1992 (Box 25, Folder 2)
- Imports Demonstration, 1984-1985 (Box 25, Folder 3)
- Independent Political Reform Commission, 1986 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  May 1
- India, 1988 (Box 25, Folder 5)
- Industrial Cooperation Council New York State, 1988 (Box 25, Folder 6)
- Industrial Policy, 1984 (Box 25, Folder 7)
- Industrial Relations Council, 1986 (Box 25, Folder 8)
- Industrial Relations Research Association Chapter Advisory, 1989 (Box 25, Folder 9)
- Industrial Relations Research Association Chapter Representatives, 1989 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  June 14
- Industrial Relations Research Association Winter Meeting, 1989-1993 (Box 25, Folder 11)
- Industrial Relations Research Association, 1989 (Box 25, Folder 12)
- Industrial Relations Research Association, 1987-1989 (Box 25, Folder 13)
- Industrial Relations Research Association - New York, 1988 (Box 25, Folder 14)
- Industrial Relations Research Association Publications, 1986-1992 (Box 25, Folder 15)
- Industrial Relations Research Association - Review Commission, 1988 (Box 25, Folder 16)
- Industrial Union Department, 1982 (Box 25, Folder 17)
- Industrial Social Welfare Center, 1973-1975 (Box 25, Folder 18)
- The Industry, 1973-1992 (Box 25, Folder 19)
- The Industry - Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union, 1992 (Box 25, Folder 20)
- Automation, 1966-1972 (Box 25, Folder 21)
- Industry - Women, 1981-1985 (Box 25, Folder 22)
- Industry - Labor Council, 1981-1988 (Box 25, Folder 23)
- Industry Labor Council Handicapped Individuals, 1976-1990 (Box 25, Folder 24)
- The Industry - Retail, 1972 (Box 25, Folder 25)
- Institute for American Values, 1988-1992 (Box 25, Folder 26)
- Industry - Shirts, 1974 (Box 26, Folder 1)
- Industry - Uniforms, 1975 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  June 26
- The Industry - Union Label (Box 26, Folder 3)
- The Inheritance - Film, 1977-1988 (Box 26, Folder 4)
- Insurance - Women, 1982 (Box 26, Folder 5)
- Infant Care, 1986 (Box 26, Folder 6)
- Institute for Families and Children, 1992-1993 (Box 26, Folder 7)
- The Industry - Organizing, 1974 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  September 10
- Japan Trip, 1992-1993 (Box 26, Folder 9)
- Japan, 1982-1992 (Box 26, Folder 10)
- Jewish Daily Forward, 1980 (Box 26, Folder 11)
- Jewish Frontier, 1981 (Box 26, Folder 12)
- Jewish Labor Committee, 1974-1987 (Box 26, Folder 13)
- Jewish Museum, 1992 (Box 26, Folder 14)
- Job Application, 1981-1989 (Box 26, Folder 15)
- Job - Bias, 1977-1984 (Box 26, Folder 16)
- Job Opportunity, 1991-1993 (Box 26, Folder 17)
- Job Path, 1982 (Box 26, Folder 18)
- Jobs, 1985 (Box 26, Folder 19)
- Job Placement, 1976-1992 (Box 26, Folder 20)
- Jobs with Justice, 1988 (Box 26, Folder 21)
- Job Match, 1985 (Box 26, Folder 22)
- Baltimore Joint Board, 1973-1977 (Box 26, Folder 23)
- California Joint Board, 1974-1978 (Box 26, Folder 24)
- Joint Board - Central States, 1972-1988 (Box 26, Folder 25)
- Joint Board - Chicago, 1974-1977 (Box 26, Folder 26)
- Joint Board - Chicago and Central States, 1977-1983 (Box 26, Folder 27)
- Joint Board - Cleveland, 1975-1976 (Box 26, Folder 28)
- Joint Board - Eastern Pennsylvania, 1977 (Box 26, Folder 29)
- El Paso Joint Board, 1975-1977 (Box 26, Folder 30)
- Chicago Joint Board Reports, 1975 (Box 26, Folder 31)
- Joint Board - Lehigh Valley (Box 26, Folder 32)
- Joint Board - Los Angeles, 1974-1977 (Box 26, Folder 33)
- Midwest Joint Board, 1972-1977 (Box 26, Folder 34)
- Minnesota Joint Board, 1973-1983 (Box 26, Folder 35)
- Joint Board - Montreal (Box 26, Folder 36)
- Joint Board Nebraska, 1975-1977 (Box 26, Folder 37)
- New England - Joint Board, 1973-1987 (Box 26, Folder 38)
- Joint Board New York, 1976-1983 (Box 26, Folder 39)
- New Orleans Joint Board, 1973-1975 (Box 26, Folder 40)
- Joint Board Ohio, 1976 (Box 26, Folder 41)
- Pennsylvania Joint Board, 1973 (Box 26, Folder 42)
- Philadelphia Joint Board, 1972-1975 (Box 26, Folder 43)
- Pittsburgh Joint Board, 1971-1980 (Box 26, Folder 44)
- Joint Board - Puerto Rico, 1975 (Box 26, Folder 45)
  March 3
- Rochester Joint Board, 1985 (Box 26, Folder 46)
- Joint Board - San Antonio, 1973-1975 (Box 26, Folder 47)
- Scranton - Wilkes Barre Joint Board, 1973-1974 (Box 27, Folder 1)
- Joint Board - Southeastern, 1976-1989 (Box 27, Folder 2)
- Joint Board Southern Department, 1976 (Box 27, Folder 3)
- Joint Board - Southern Textile Regional, 1987 (Box 27, Folder 4)
- Southwest Regional Joint Board, 1973-1989 (Box 27, Folder 5)
- Tennessee Joint Board, 1974-1975 (Box 27, Folder 6)
- Joint Board - Toledo, 1977 (Box 27, Folder 7)
- Joint Board - Toronto, 1973-1978 (Box 27, Folder 8)
- Joint Board - Virginia, 1978 (Box 27, Folder 9)
- Joint Board - Cheyenne, Wyoming, 1976 (Box 27, Folder 10)
- Kamaiko Fund for Social Work, 1992 (Box 27, Folder 11)
- Martin Luther King, 1983-1984 (Box 27, Folder 12)
- Korea, 1980 (Box 27, Folder 13)
- Kuwait (Box 27, Folder 14)
- Labor Becoming Owners, 1990 (Box 27, Folder 15)
- Labor College, 1973 (Box 27, Folder 16)
- Labor Council for Latin American Advancement, 1985-1990 (Box 27, Folder 17)
- Labor Day Messages, 1983-1992 (Box 27, Folder 18)
- Labor Day Parade - 1983, 1982-1983 (Box 27, Folder 19)
- Labor Economics, 1988 (Box 27, Folder 20)
  March 16
- Labor Education, 1988 (Box 27, Folder 21)
- Labor Forum Planning Meeting, 1977 (Box 27, Folder 22)
  January 5
- Labor Heritage Foundation, 1989-1993 (Box 27, Folder 23)
- Labor History, 1964-1990 (Box 27, Folder 24)
- Labor History, 1976 (Box 27, Folder 25)
- Labor History Association - New York, 1987 (Box 27, Folder 26)
- Labor Institute for Human Enrichment, 1981 (Box 27, Folder 27)
- Labor Institute of Public Affairs, 1986 (Box 27, Folder 28)
- Labor Law - Reform, 1978-1983 (Box 27, Folder 29)
- Labor Leadership, 1988-1991 (Box 27, Folder 30)
- Labor Legislation, 1992 (Box 27, Folder 31)
- Labor Management Committee Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union, 1991 (Box 27, Folder 32)
- Labor Management Relations, 1989 (Box 27, Folder 33)
- Labor Movement, 1975-1990 (Box 27, Folder 34)
- Labor - New York (Box 27, Folder 35)
- Labor Party, 1991 (Box 27, Folder 36)
- Labor for Peace, 1991 (Box 27, Folder 37)
- Labor People (Box 27, Folder 38)
- Labor Research Association, 1977 (Box 27, Folder 39)
- Labor Theatre, 1979-1987 (Box 27, Folder 40)
- Labor Theatre, 1977-1981 (Box 27, Folder 41)
- Labor Unity, 1976-1992 (Box 27, Folder 42)
- Latin America, 1984-1990 (Box 27, Folder 43)
- Layoffs, 1975 (Box 27, Folder 44)
- Leadership Conference on Civil Rights, 1988 (Box 27, Folder 45)
  December 21
- League for Industrial Democracy, 1974-1984 (Box 27, Folder 46)
- League of Women Voters, 1986 (Box 27, Folder 47)
- Lebanon, 1983-1984 (Box 27, Folder 48)
- Legal Services, 1973 (Box 27, Folder 49)
- Legal Services - Resource Center for Consumers, 1974 (Box 27, Folder 50)
  May 10
- Legislative News, 1973 (Box 27, Folder 51)
- Letters from Members Miscellaneous, 1984 (Box 27, Folder 52)
- Leverage Buyouts (Box 27, Folder 53)
- Levi Strauss Foundation, 1979 (Box 27, Folder 54)
- Liberal Party, 1978 (Box 27, Folder 55)
- S. Lichtenburg and Co., Inc., 1988-1991 (Box 27, Folder 56)
- Long Island Power Authority (LIPA), 1989 (Box 27, Folder 57)
  February 8
- Litton, 1983 (Box 27, Folder 58)
- Lobbyists, 1987 (Box 27, Folder 59)
  July 27
- Local 153 Contract Negotiation, 1987 (Box 27, Folder 60)
  September 28
- Local 149, 1992 (Box 27, Folder 61)
- Local 1199, 1972-1973 (Box 27, Folder 62)
- Local 2H (Box 27, Folder 63)
- Long Beach, 1990 (Box 27, Folder 64)
  June 27
- Long Term Campaign, 1990 (Box 27, Folder 65)
- Long Term Care, 1989-1990 (Box 27, Folder 66)
- Majority Coalition, 1991-1992 (Box 27, Folder 67)
- Mandatory Retirement, 1976-1977 (Box 27, Folder 68)
- Comprehensive Training and Employment Act (CTEA), 1976 (Box 27, Folder 69)
- Center for Science in the Public Interest, 1974 (Box 27, Folder 70)
- Central Labor Council (Box 27, Folder 71)
- Center for Women in Government, 1978-1979 (Box 27, Folder 72)
- Center for Studies of Metropolitan Problems, 1978 (Box 27, Folder 73)
- Center for Public Integrity, 1990 (Box 28, Folder 1)
- Center for Policy Alternatives, 1992-1993 (Box 28, Folder 2)
- California Labor Federation, 1981-1986 (Box 28, Folder 3)
- Cambodia, 1980 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  January 24
- Center for Labor Research and Studies, 1982-1987 (Box 28, Folder 5)
- Census, 1989 (Box 28, Folder 6)
- Caterers, 1988 (Box 28, Folder 7)
- Catalyst, 1980-1982 (Box 28, Folder 8)
- Carter, Jimmy, 1980 (Box 28, Folder 9)
- Carnegie Mellon, 1987 (Box 28, Folder 10)
  November 9
- Carey, Hugh L., 1978 (Box 28, Folder 11)
  July 17
- Career Guidance, 1983 (Box 28, Folder 12)
- Cardio-Pulmonary Resuscitation, 1984 (Box 28, Folder 13)
  March 27
- Cannon Mills, 1990-1991 (Box 28, Folder 14)
- Cannon Women, 1974-1979 (Box 28, Folder 15)
- Canada, 1972-1990 (Box 28, Folder 16)
- Caban, Kilmer, 1992 (Box 28, Folder 17)
- Dorian, Linda C., 1988 (Box 28, Folder 18)
  November 7
- Business and Professional Women's Foundation, 1982-1983 (Box 28, Folder 19)
- Botto House, 1983-1992 (Box 28, Folder 20)
- Bork, Robert, Nomination, 1987 (Box 28, Folder 21)
- Boycott British Goods Committee, 1983 (Box 28, Folder 22)
- Bread and Roses, 1980-1981 (Box 28, Folder 23)
- Boro Medical Center, 1985 (Box 28, Folder 24)
- Building Trades, 1993 (Box 28, Folder 25)
  March 9
- Business Day, 1980 (Box 28, Folder 26)
  January 19
- Budget, 1980-1981 (Box 28, Folder 27)
- Boy Scouts, 1987 (Box 28, Folder 28)
- Brussels, 1983-1987 (Box 28, Folder 29)
- Blood Bank, 1975-1989 (Box 28, Folder 30)
- Blindness, 1977 (Box 28, Folder 31)
- Blue Collar, 1974 (Box 28, Folder 32)
- Nelson Mandela, 1990 (Box 28, Folder 33)
  June 25
- Manpower - Article (Box 28, Folder 34)
- Manpower - National, 1977-1984 (Box 28, Folder 35)
- March of Dimes, 1976-1991 (Box 28, Folder 36)
- Productivity through Work Innovations, 1981 (Box 28, Folder 37)
  April
- Progressive alliance, 1979 (Box 28, Folder 38)
- Project South Africa, 1986 (Box 28, Folder 39)
- Public Affairs, 1980-1982 (Box 28, Folder 40)
- Product Liability Law, 1985-1986 (Box 28, Folder 41)
- Recommendations, 1979-1990 (Box 28, Folder 42)
- Reagan and Women, 1981-1984 (Box 28, Folder 43)
- Reagan, 1981-1984 (Box 28, Folder 44)
- Rainbow Coalition, 1990-1992 (Box 28, Folder 45)
- Quotes (Box 28, Folder 46)
- Quality of Working Life, 1981-1982 (Box 28, Folder 47)
- Public Domain, 1989-1990 (Box 29, Folder 1)
- Religion and Labor, 1983-1991 (Box 29, Folder 2)
- Relief Programs, 1976 (Box 29, Folder 3)
- Institute for Rehabilitation and Disability Management, 1984 (Box 29, Folder 4)
- Regional Plan Association, 1978-1983 (Box 29, Folder 5)
- Regional Conferences - Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union, 1988 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  June 20
- Red Cross, 1976-1992 (Box 29, Folder 7)
- Retired Staff, 1981 (Box 29, Folder 8)
- Retired Members - Working, 1984 (Box 29, Folder 9)
- Retail Insurance, 1972-1973 (Box 29, Folder 10)
- Resource Center for Consumers of Legal Services, 1975 (Box 29, Folder 11)
- Resignations, 1977 (Box 29, Folder 12)
  October 5
- Research, 1977-1982 (Box 29, Folder 13)
- Replacement Workers, 1990 (Box 29, Folder 14)
- Retirees - American Federation of Labor - Congress of Industrial Organizations, 1983-1988 (Box 29, Folder 15)
- Retirees - Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union, 1981-1988 (Box 29, Folder 16)
- Retirees, 1988-1990 (Box 29, Folder 17)
- Retiree - New York, 1984-1985 (Box 29, Folder 18)
- Retirees - Florida, 1983-1989 (Box 29, Folder 19)
- Retiree Programs, 1991 (Box 29, Folder 20)
- Retiree Council - New York - Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union, 1985 (Box 29, Folder 21)
- Right Wing, 1977-1978 (Box 29, Folder 22)
- Right to Work, 1974-1977 (Box 29, Folder 23)
- Revson Fellows, 1990 (Box 29, Folder 24)
- Reverse Discrimination, 1977 (Box 29, Folder 25)
  September 19
- Revenue Sharing, 1972 (Box 29, Folder 26)
- Retraining, 1990 (Box 29, Folder 27)
  April 23
- Retirement, 1992 (Box 29, Folder 28)
  February 1
- Retirees - Women, 1986 (Box 29, Folder 29)
- Ron Rosenberg, 1991 (Box 29, Folder 30)
- Roosevelt Island, 1989 (Box 29, Folder 31)
- Roosevelt Institute, 1988-1989 (Box 29, Folder 32)
- Rome, 1993 (Box 29, Folder 33)
- Rochdale Institute, 1974-1983 (Box 29, Folder 34)
- Sallee Scholarship, 1989 (Box 29, Folder 35)
- S. Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union, 1990 (Box 29, Folder 36)
- Rutgers Book, 1991 (Box 29, Folder 37)
  July 29
- Richard Rothstein, 1990 (Box 29, Folder 38)
  September 27
- Roundabout Theater, 1976-1977 (Box 29, Folder 39)
- Strategic Arms Limitation Treaty (SALT), 1979 (Box 29, Folder 40)
- Savings and Loops, 1991 (Box 29, Folder 41)
- Scholarships - Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union, 1979 (Box 29, Folder 42)
- Select Committee on Immigration and Refugee Policy, 1979 (Box 29, Folder 43)
  November 16
- Senior Citizens, 1973 (Box 29, Folder 44)
- Senior Citizens for Better Government, 1977 (Box 29, Folder 45)
- Seniors - New York, 1975 (Box 29, Folder 46)
- Seniority, 1977-1984 (Box 29, Folder 47)
- Social Services American Federation of Labor - Congress of Industrial Organizations, 1989 (Box 29, Folder 48)
- Social Services Committees, 1989-1990 (Box 29, Folder 49)
- Social Services and ALICO, 1993 (Box 29, Folder 50)
- Social Security - Women, 1979-1980 (Box 29, Folder 51)
- Social Security Commission Articles, 1979-1991 (Box 29, Folder 52)
- Social Services Department - Finance, 1985-1993 (Box 30, Folder 1)
- Social Services, 1982-1992 (Box 30, Folder 2)
- Social Security - Women, 1979-1984 (Box 30, Folder 3)
- Social Security Commission Disability Insurance, 1972-1977 (Box 30, Folder 4)
- Commission Travel Information, 1979-1980 (Box 30, Folder 5)
- Social Security Commission Expenses, 1979 (Box 30, Folder 6)
- Social Security Commission Staff, 1979 (Box 30, Folder 7)
- Socialists, 1973 (Box 30, Folder 8)
- Social Benefits, 1988-1991 (Box 30, Folder 9)
- Social Justice, 1977 (Box 30, Folder 10)
- Social Reform, 1973 (Box 30, Folder 11)
- Social Security, 1985-1990 (Box 30, Folder 12)
- Social Security Committee American Federation of Labor - Congress of Industrial Organizations, 1988 (Box 30, Folder 13)
- Sex Discrimination, 1975-1986 (Box 30, Folder 14)
- Jack Sheinkman, 1987 (Box 30, Folder 15)
- Sheltered Workshops (Box 30, Folder 16)
- Shoe Division, 1980-1985 (Box 30, Folder 17)
- Shoeworkers Grant, 1986-1987 (Box 30, Folder 18)
- Shop Stewards Training (Box 30, Folder 19)
- Skilled Worker Emeritus, 1991 (Box 30, Folder 20)
- Smithsonian Institute, 1974-1975 (Box 30, Folder 21)
- Seniority and Layoffs, 1975 (Box 30, Folder 22)
- Service Employees Registration and Voter Education Campaign (SERVE), 1987 (Box 30, Folder 23)
- Settlement Housing Fund, 1973-1976 (Box 30, Folder 24)
- 75th Anniversary Dinner and Sidney Hillman Lunch, 1989 (Box 30, Folder 25)
- Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union - Sexual Harassment, 1981-1991 (Box 30, Folder 26)
- Social Service Report - General Executive Board, 1991 (Box 30, Folder 27)
- Social Services in the Year 2000, 1984 (Box 30, Folder 28)
- Social Services Staff, 1986-1989 (Box 30, Folder 29)
- Social Services Office Staff Meetings, 1982-1985 (Box 30, Folder 30)
- Social Services - State of New York, 1983-1987 (Box 30, Folder 31)
- Solidarity Day - III, 1991 (Box 30, Folder 32)
- Solidarity Day March, 1981 (Box 30, Folder 33)
- South Africa, 1984-1990 (Box 31, Folder 1)
- Southern Department, 1976 (Box 31, Folder 2)
- Southern Exposure, 1976-1980 (Box 31, Folder 3)
- Southern Labor History Conference, 1978 (Box 31, Folder 4)
- Southern Regional - Georgia Joint Board, 1991-1993 (Box 31, Folder 5)
- Staff Attendance, 1983-1985 (Box 31, Folder 6)
- Staff - Job Description, 1988 (Box 31, Folder 7)
- Staff List (Box 31, Folder 8)
- Staff Newsletter, 1972-1977 (Box 31, Folder 9)
- Steel Imports, 1983 (Box 31, Folder 10)
- J.P. Stevens (Box 31, Folder 11)
- Stress, 1979-1982 (Box 31, Folder 12)
- Striker Replacement, 1990-1991 (Box 31, Folder 13)
- Strike Support, 1986-1989 (Box 31, Folder 14)
- Student Interns, 1981-1982 (Box 31, Folder 15)
- Substance Abuse and Drug, 1989-1990 (Box 31, Folder 16)
- Summer School - Social Services, 1975 (Box 31, Folder 17)
- Support Letters, 1981 (Box 31, Folder 18)
- Support Services Alliance, 1977 (Box 31, Folder 19)
- Supreme Court Decisions, 1989 (Box 31, Folder 20)
- Sweatshops, 1981 (Box 31, Folder 21)
- Sweden, 1981-1987 (Box 31, Folder 22)
- Sylvis Said, 1984-1989 (Box 31, Folder 23)
- Sympathy Messages, 1980-1986 (Box 31, Folder 24)
- Synthetic Fibers and Film Division, 1977 (Box 31, Folder 25)
- T-Shirts (Box 31, Folder 26)
- Target, 1988 (Box 31, Folder 27)
- Task Force for Democracy, 1981 (Box 31, Folder 28)
- Tax-Earned Income Tax Credit, 1988-1989 (Box 31, Folder 29)
- Taxes - General, 1974-1992 (Box 31, Folder 30)
- Tax Reform, 1979-1985 (Box 31, Folder 31)
- Technology, 1984 (Box 31, Folder 32)
- Telegram, 1977 (Box 31, Folder 33)
- Textile and Apparel Trade Act, 1990 (Box 31, Folder 34)
- Textile Industry, 1976-1984 (Box 31, Folder 35)
- Textile Merger, 1976-1982 (Box 31, Folder 36)
- Textile - Locals, 1981 (Box 31, Folder 37)
- Textile Machinery, 1990 (Box 31, Folder 38)
- Textile Workers Union of America - Hudson Valley Joint Board, 1975-1976 (Box 31, Folder 39)
- Time Magazine, 1992 (Box 31, Folder 40)
  February 24
- Title V, 1976 (Box 31, Folder 41)
- Title IX and Title X, 1975 (Box 31, Folder 42)
- Title XX - New York, 1975 (Box 31, Folder 43)
- To Life, 1984-1985 (Box 31, Folder 44)
- Toronto, 1989 (Box 31, Folder 45)
- National Association of Social Workers, Inc., 1985 (Box 31, Folder 46)
- National Center-Employment Handicapped, Human Resource Center, 1987 (Box 31, Folder 47)
- School Desegregation, 1976 (Box 31, Folder 48)
- National Child Labor Committee, 1980-1985 (Box 31, Folder 49)
- National Coalition Against Censorship, 1983-1992 (Box 31, Folder 50)
- National Commission on Unemployment Compensation, 1979 (Box 31, Folder 51)
  April 4
- National Commission on Working Women, 1979-1983 (Box 31, Folder 52)
- National Committee on Pay Equity, 1988-1992 (Box 31, Folder 53)
- National Committee for Full Employment, 1988 (Box 32, Folder 1)
- National Conference of Christians and Jews, 1985 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  September 13
- National Committee for Full Employment - Board, 1987 (Box 32, Folder 3)
- National Conference on Social Welfare (Box 32, Folder 4)
- National Consumer Center for Legal Services, 1974-1975 (Box 32, Folder 5)
- National Consumer Cooperative Bank, 1978 (Box 32, Folder 6)
- National Consumers League, 1976-1992 (Box 32, Folder 7)
- National Council on the Aging, 1982-1993 (Box 32, Folder 8)
- Anderson, Sally and Frank, 1978 (Box 32, Folder 9)
- Adams, Kay Francis, 1977-1978 (Box 32, Folder 10)
- Anderson, Janie Beel and Curtis, 1978 (Box 32, Folder 11)
- Blanton, Martha Ann and Jack, 1978 (Box 32, Folder 12)
- Clark, Ethel, 1977-1978 (Box 32, Folder 13)
- Daniel, Geneva, 1978-1979 (Box 32, Folder 14)
- Ehlenbach, Russell L., 1978 (Box 32, Folder 15)
- Arlene, Joanson, 1978 (Box 32, Folder 16)
- Mason, Ora, 1978 (Box 32, Folder 17)
- McAlister, Patricia, 1978 (Box 32, Folder 18)
- McMaron, Lucille CLOSED, 1978 (Box 32, Folder 19)
- McSaka, Cora, 1978 (Box 32, Folder 20)
- Palario, Hector and Dora, 1979 (Box 32, Folder 21)
- Parrington, Phyllis, 1975-1978 (Box 32, Folder 22)
- Robinson, Juanita, 1978 (Box 32, Folder 23)
- Roberts, Sherrill and Wayne, 1978 (Box 32, Folder 24)
- Oliver, Nora Lee, 1978 (Box 32, Folder 25)
- Moates, Jessie, 1978 (Box 32, Folder 26)
- Lavell, Faye, 1978 (Box 32, Folder 27)
- Jenkins, Leslie and Gail, 1978 (Box 32, Folder 28)
- Sheppard, Lisa, 1978 (Box 32, Folder 29)
- Smith, Billy and Patricia, J.P. Stephens, 1978 (Box 32, Folder 30)
- Suttles, Jessie, 1978 (Box 32, Folder 31)
- Thompson, Wanda, 1978 (Box 32, Folder 32)
- Turner, James A., 1978 (Box 32, Folder 33)
- Debra Ware, 1978 (Box 32, Folder 34)
- Williams, Dorothy and Jessie Gene Sr., 1978 (Box 32, Folder 35)
- Whitlock Ralph, 1978 (Box 32, Folder 36)
- Zinn, Paul, 1979 (Box 32, Folder 37)